How Thelma and Louise of us.
(Bernadette:)Raj, why don't I care
about anything?
(Raj:)I'm sorry?
(Bernadette:)It's my baby.
I-I should care about
nurseries and colors,
(Bernadette:)and I don't--
what's wrong with me?
(Raj:)Well, crime-scene photos
near your crib spring to mind.
(Bernadette:)I keep waiting
to feel excited,
(Bernadette:)but it's not happening.
(Bernadette:)What if it
never happens?
(Scene:)Bernadette,
come on, look,
(Raj:)you're overthinking this,
okay?
(Raj:)You're gonna be
an amazing mom.
(Raj:)Even if you don't
believe it,
(Raj:)I know you have
maternal instincts.
(Bernadette:)Once, I was supposed
to babysit my brothers.
Our neighbor found them
naked in the backyard
(Bernadette:)eating crickets.
(Raj:)Happy and well-fed.
(Raj:)You see, that's what
I'm taking from that story.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, can I ask you
a question?
(Leonard:)Is it about the
rotational symmetries
(Leonard:)you should be
figuring out
(Leonard:)or your fake
caffeine problem?